[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Mid Terms CAL21",
    "startDate": "2020-07-19T13:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-07-18T19:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "75",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 3,
        "questionText": "Explain life.",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "questionText": "What is this?",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["tree", "roof", "floor", "knife"],
        "correctAnswer": "floor"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "questionText": "7>6",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Final CAL21",
    "startDate": "2020-11-06T13:09:57-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-12-25T13:10:07-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": []
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "course": 2,
    "examTitle": "ABCD Intro Mid Semeester",
    "startDate": "2020-07-26T07:28:17-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-08-31T12:28:33-05:00",
    "duaration": "75",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 4,
        "questionText": "What is this",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "questionText": "What's your name?",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "questionText": "Am I real?",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "questionText": "jiojiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["wwdd, wsokde, skwsk, sokws"],
        "correctAnswer": "wsokde"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Final",
    "startDate": "2020-07-29T19:35:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-07-30T19:35:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": []
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Finals for Course Math",
    "startDate": "2020-10-11T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-11-11T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": []
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Finals for English 2",
    "startDate": "2020-10-11T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-11-11T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 8,
        "questionText": "What is this? ->>",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["Arrow", "Triangle", "Square", "Circle"],
        "correctAnswer": "Arrow"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Finals of My Life",
    "startDate": "2020-10-11T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-11-11T10:10:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 9,
        "questionText": "What is this? -->>",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["Arrow", "Triangle", "Circle", "Square"],
        "correctAnswer": "Arrow"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "questionText": "Explain your life and struggles",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Meh",
    "startDate": "2020-07-30T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-10-10T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 11,
        "questionText": "Test",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correctAnswer": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "questionText": "Essay",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Final",
    "startDate": "2020-08-06T00:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-08-08T23:59:59-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 13,
        "questionText": "Question 3",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["a", "s", "d", "f"],
        "correctAnswer": "f"
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "questionText": "Yaq",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["q", "w", "e", "r"],
        "correctAnswer": "w"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-10-12T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-10-14T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 15,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 17,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-10-12T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-10-14T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 18,
        "questionText": "ioijioji",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      },
      {
        "id": 19,
        "questionText": "nlkmlkmkl",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["jjio", "jiojiojio", "jiojioj", "iojioj"],
        "correctAnswer": "jiojiojio"
      },
      {
        "id": 20,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Final",
    "startDate": "2020-08-06T00:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-08-08T23:59:59-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 24,
        "questionText": "Question 3",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["a", "s", "d", "f"],
        "correctAnswer": "f"
      },
      {
        "id": 25,
        "questionText": "Yaq",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["q", "w", "e", "r"],
        "correctAnswer": "w"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "It was me, Dio!",
    "startDate": "2020-09-12T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-10-14T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 21,
        "questionText": "jiojiojioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 22,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      },
      {
        "id": 23,
        "questionText": "jiojiojioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["oijoi", "iojiojio", "jiojoimokm", "omoimim"],
        "correctAnswer": "oijoi"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "Testing MCQ",
    "startDate": "2020-08-21T00:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-09-21T23:59:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 26,
        "questionText": "one",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["4", "1", "2", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": 27,
        "questionText": "two",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["3", "1", "2", "4"],
        "correctAnswer": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": 28,
        "questionText": "three",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["3", "2", "1", "4"],
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-10-12T10:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-10-14T10:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 29,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 30,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 31,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-10-12T09:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-10-14T09:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 32,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 33,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 34,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-09-12T09:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-09-14T09:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 35,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 36,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 37,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-09-02T09:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-09-04T09:00:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 38,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 39,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 40,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-09-02T09:01:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-09-04T09:01:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 41,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 42,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 43,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-08-23T18:00:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-11-25T23:59:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 44,
        "questionText": "klmklmklm",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-09-02T09:01:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-09-04T09:01:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 45,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 46,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 47,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "course": 1,
    "examTitle": "CS400",
    "startDate": "2020-09-02T09:01:00-05:00",
    "endDate": "2020-09-04T09:01:00-05:00",
    "duaration": "120",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 48,
        "questionText": "joijiojio",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["ijioj", "iojoij", "oijioji", "ojiojio"],
        "correctAnswer": "iojoij"
      },
      {
        "id": 49,
        "questionText": "oijoijioj",
        "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "correctAnswer": "True"
      },
      {
        "id": 50,
        "questionText": "njljkj",
        "questionType": "Long Answer",
        "options": [],
        "correctAnswer": ""
      }
    ]
  }
]
